I don't know why I really like to end on
like even or like like fives or tens so
this will be number forty and I can't
believe I've done this all in one day I
thought this would be at least four days
worth or 100 days is ridiculous to me I
love this this is amazing this is so
inspiring so I do 440 now do you know
what it's gonna be
oh wait then because I walk straight
quickly I'm here to this so you don't
get to see the beautiful roses and I'm
going to do which means if I'm look at
you I can't really do that can I why did
you look at you I'm not going to look at
you
sorry I do number 40
one apples
right now I'm getting a knowledge here
so it's like applesauce and I know how
to make applesauce I don't think it's
like complicated those YouTube videos
but for things like making caper and
sauerkraut and other how to grow a
garden how to do woodworking how to do
where I mean YouTube works but a lot of
times you need the resource and stuff
but having experts that you can easily
hire and coordinate group sweat so say
okay I want to learn how to make yogurt
and therefore someone's like line how to
make yogurt pay me 10 bucks to teach you
but get 10 people together so making
hundred bucks and it's a way for people
to make money off their skill and
therefore may have a living and also to
have yeah just have it accessible
because I can afford $10 learn yoga and
I couldn't afford a hundred dollars to
learn to yogurt so that is Apple number
40 and so I was walking around but it
felt right at the moment